bodyjewelleryshop.co.uk 2008-06-27

# BodyJewelleryShop.com Privacy Statement

BodyJewelleryShop.com is comitted to ensuring the privacy and protection of our visitors.

Access  
You may browse our website without any data being collected from you, however in order to enjoy a tailored browsing and shopping experience, we offer you the ability to register an account with us.

Ordering from BodyJewelleryShop.com  
You do not have to have an account in order to purchase goods from BodyJewelleryShop.com. When you add items to your cart, a file is created on our server which stores details of your purchases. This file is linked uniquely to your browsing session and cannot be viewed by anyone else.  
When you complete your order, we ask for personal information about you, such as your full name, address, e-mail address, phone number and credit card details. This data will only be shared with our payment service provider and courier services, and only for the purposes of processing and shipping your order.  
All sensitive data is transmitted via an industry standard 128-bit secure socket layer connection.  
We do not store your payment details 

We collect anonymous, non-personal data, such as how many times a product is purchased or viewed, in order to continually modify our website to suit the browsing trends of our users.  

Your account  
When you register for an account with BodyJewelleryShop.com, we require that you give us a valid e-mail address. This is so that our system can verify your registration and issue you with a personal password to allow you access to your member area.   
You can use your member account to store your personal data, for the purposes of making orders with BodyJewelleryShop.com. You can also use your account to sign up for email updates, or use our community pages.   
Our community pages allow you to share personal information about yourself for other users to see. This information is optional.

The 'remember me' feature is an automatic login process which creates a cookie on the hard drive of your computer containing a unique login ID, thereby avoiding the need to enter your login details upon subsequent visits to BodyJewelleryShop.com. Do not select this option if you share this computer with others since personal or member only information will be accessible by other users.  

Your data  
We do not automatically collect personal data about you.  
We do not collect information about our you from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations  
We do not share any personal data with any 3rd part organisation or institution, except for the purposes of processing your order as detailed above, or if required to do so by law.  

Security  
BodyJewelleryShop.com is protected by the very best in [secure server technology](http://www.thawte.com/cgi/server/certdetails.exe?referer=http://www.BodyJewelleryShop.com), provided by [Thawte](http://www.thawte.com/), one of the world's leading secure certificate specialists.  
We are accredited by [ISIS](http://isis.imrg.org/screens/VerifyMerchantFrame.asp?guid=6AD2E074-DFEE-4E53-9608-A973EB774C65) (Internet shopping is safe), a government run organisation created to protect the interests of consumers purchasing online.  
Our servers are held in a secure data centre located in the UK, and are protected by an inpenetratable firewall setup that allows for no unauthorised access.

External websites   
This privacy policy covers the usage of BodyJewelleryShop.com only. Where we have linked to external sites, a different privacy policiy may apply.

|    

Shopping Cart

Go to the **online store** to start shopping!

* * *

Currency Display: 

 More Currencies:

Member Login

About Body Jewellery Shop

Jewellery Essentials
